From public profile



Hansel Lander R . 3rd In

Director Hland Agency

INSTITUTO DE DISEÑO DE CARACAS · Venezuela · Marketing and Advertising · 500+ &

- @ Add email
- Add phone number
- in Public profile Search on Bing

•••

Profile Projects (0) Messages (0) Feedback (0) Attachments (0) Recruiting Activi

No recruiting activity

Summary

A lo largo de los últimos 10 años he trabajado con marcas como Bimbo, General Motors, Digitel, Directv, Tupperware, Destilo, Joyería Daoro, Ulysse Nardin, Pandora, Le collezioni, Salvatore Ferragamo, Bally, Joyería Sami Bazzi, Century 21, entre otros **See less of summary**

Experience

HLAND agency

8 yrs 8 mos

Director

Aug 2015 - Present • 7 yrs 10 mos

Skills: Adobe InDesign • Desarrollo web • Diseño • Branding • Material de marketing • Presentaciones • Aptitudes para la supervisión • Dirección creativa • Marketing de productos • Comunicaciones de medios sociales • Marca e identidad • Adobe Creative Suite • Diseño de logotipos • Gráficos • Adobe Illustrator

Director

Oct 2014 - Present • 8 yrs 8 mos

Skills: Adobe InDesign • Desarrollo web • Diseño • Branding • Material de marketing • Presentaciones • Aptitudes para la supervisión • Dirección creativa • Marketing de productos • Comunicaciones de medios sociales • Marca e identidad • Adobe Creative Suite • Diseño de logotipos • Gráficos • Adobe Illustrator

Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann

11 yrs 5 mos

Director de arte

Jan 2012 - Present • 11 yrs 5 mos

Skills: Desarrollo web • Diseño • Branding • Material de marketing • Presentaciones • Aptitudes para la supervisión • Dirección creativa • Marketing de productos •

Comunicaciones de medios sociales • Marca e identidad • Adobe Creative Suite • Diseño de logotipos • Gráficos • Adobe Illustrator

Director de arte

Jan 2012 - Aug 2015 • 3 yrs 8 mos

Skills: Adobe InDesign • Desarrollo web • Diseño • Branding • Material de marketing • Presentaciones • Aptitudes para la supervisión • Dirección creativa • Marketing de productos • Comunicaciones de medios sociales • Marca e identidad • Adobe Creative Suite • Diseño de logotipos • Gráficos • Adobe Illustrator

ART DIRECTOR

VHLUXE MEDIA GROUP

Jun 2009 - Present • 14 yrs

Skills: Adobe InDesign • Desarrollo web • Branding • Material de marketing • Presentaciones • Aptitudes para la supervisión • Dirección creativa • Marketing de productos • Comunicaciones de medios sociales • Marca e identidad • Adobe Creative Suite • Diseño de logotipos • Gráficos • Adobe Illustrator

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

ONTIME MAGAZINE

Apr 2007 - May 2009 • 2 yrs 2 mos

Skills: Adobe InDesign • Desarrollo web • Branding • Material de marketing • Presentaciones • Aptitudes para la supervisión • Dirección creativa • Marketing de productos • Comunicaciones de medios sociales • Marca e identidad • Adobe Creative Suite • Diseño de logotipos • Gráficos • Adobe Illustrator

Education

INSTITUTO DE DISEÑO DE CARACAS

TECNICO • DISEÑO 2001 - 2004

POSA ESTUDIO

Cursos Flash Avanzado/Dreamweaver/after effects/certificación Adobe 2012 - 2013

Skills (50)

Marketing en Internet

Mercadotecnia

Email Marketing



1 endorsement

Comunicaciones de marketing



2 8 endorsements

Marketing de productos

Director at HLAND agency

Director at HLAND Agency

Director de arte at Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann

Show all 8 details ~

Social Media Marketing



4 endorsements

Mercadotecnia en medios sociales



1 7 endorsements

Diseño de logotipos

Director at HLAND agency

Director at HLAND Agency

Director de arte at Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann

Show all 8 details ~

Marca e identidad

Director at HLAND agency

Director at HLAND Agency

Director de arte at Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann

Show all 8 details ~

Diseño gráfico



11 endorsements

Graphic Design



4 endorsements

Diseño

Director at HLAND agency

Director at HLAND Agency

Director de arte at Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann

Show all 4 details ~

Art Direction



1 endorsement

Dirección artística



4 6 endorsements

Aptitudes para la supervisión

Director at HLAND agency

Director at HLAND Agency

Director de arte at Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann

Show all 6 details ~

Desarrollo web

Director at HLAND agency

Director at HLAND Agency

Director de arte at Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann

Show all 6 details ~

Online Advertising



1 endorsement

Publicidad en Internet



8 endorsements

Magazines



4 endorsements

Dirección creativa

Director at HLAND agency

Director at HLAND Agency

Director de arte at Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann

Show all 8 details ~

Branding

Director at HLAND agency

Director at HLAND Agency

Director de arte at Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann

Show all 6 details ~

Brand Management



1 endorsement

Adobe Illustrator Director at HLAND agency Director at HLAND Agency Director de arte at Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann Show all 8 details ~ Material de marketing Director at HLAND agency Director at HLAND Agency Director de arte at Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann Show all 6 details ~ **Redes sociales** 10 endorsements **Facebook** 1 endorsement **Advertising** 4 endorsements **Publicidad** 13 endorsements **Typography** 1 endorsement **Tipografía** 3 endorsements **Adobe InDesign** Director at HLAND agency Director at HLAND Agency ART DIRECTOR at VHLUXE MEDIA GROUP

Show all 5 details ~

Editorial

1 endorsement

Comunicaciones de medios sociales

Director at HLAND agency Director at HLAND Agency Director de arte at Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann Show all 8 details ~ **SEO** 1 endorsement Optimización en buscadores 3 endorsements **Marketing Communications** 3 endorsements Marketing 5 endorsements **Gráficos** Director at HLAND agency Director at HLAND Agency Director de arte at Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann Show all 8 details ~ **Fashion** 1 endorsement **Brand Development** 3 endorsements **Social Media** 4 endorsements **Publishing** 1 endorsement **Online Marketing** 1 endorsement **Digital Media** 1 endorsement **Adobe Creative Suite**

Director at HLAND agency

Director at HLAND Agency

Director de arte at Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann

Show all 8 details ~

After Effects



LinkedIn Skill Assessment badge

Presentaciones

Director at HLAND agency

Director at HLAND Agency

Director de arte at Mg ideas / Concept-Mccann

Show all 6 details ~

Adobe Photoshop



LinkedIn Skill Assessment badge

Digital Marketing



1 endorsement

Marketing digital



7 endorsements

Show fewer ^

Interests

Founder at Virgin Group



Jeff Weiner

Executive Chairman at LinkedIn / Founding Partner Next Play Ventures 10,440,110 followers

Show more ~

Personal Information



Hansel's profile

https://ve.linkedin.com/in/hansel-lander-r

Recruiting: Tools



Website

http://www.hlandagency.com (Company) http://Hansel.lander@hlandagency.com (Personal)

Notes (0)



Links (0)



Reminders (0)



Similar Profiles



Duilio Pérez Montilla · 3rd

Director Creativo

Miranda State, Venezuela

LinkedIn Member

director de arte en publicidad

Naiguatá, Vargas State, Venezuela



Yuleidy Rodriguez · 3rd

Directora de Arte Senior, Especialista en Branding, + de 7 años exp.

Venezuela

LinkedIn Member

Director de Arte Independiente

Venezuela

LinkedIn Member

Diseñador gráfico en Primera Aisve

Caracas, Federal District, Venezuela

LinkedIn Member

General Art Director

Miranda State, Venezuela

LinkedIn Member

Freelance /Graphic Design Services/ Social Network Management

Venezuela

LinkedIn Member

Director de arte ON Agencia Digital

Tachira State, Venezuela

LinkedIn Member

Director de arte Independiente

Caracas, Federal District, Venezuela

LinkedIn Member

🖊 Creo el estilo gráfico de Tu Marca o Empresa. 👚 Diseño de Logos e Identidad Visual. 📾 #...